<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<app version="1.0">
	<name>postLoader</name>
	<version>4.b24</version>
	<release_date>20120623000000</release_date>
	<coder>stfour</coder>
	<short_description>Homebrew browser, channel launcher, neek2o disc loader</short_description>
	<long_description>-------------------
What postLoader is:
-------------------
* HomeBrew Browser with subfolder and xml support
* Channel\Title\Emus\Games Browser with filters and cover
* neek2o and Uneek+DI game browser with cover support
* game loaders forwarder (for CFG, GX and WiiFlow) with cover and filters support
* DML gamecube browser with USB to SD copy feature
* Themable user interface
* Wiiload server

-------------------
Features:
-------------------

General:
* If started from priiloader it gains AHPBROT and spawn full hardware rights to homebrew applications
* Autoboot your default application\channel: If you don't press (A) in time to enter in interactive mode, postLoader will launch the predefined app (if enabled)
* Direct access to BOOTMII
* Support costom splash screen (only from SD device)
* Full support for UNEEK environment. May work under SNEEK
* Support for Wiimote and GC controllers
* Intergrated UNEEK nand switcher
* wiiload update: If you send postLoader.dol via wiiload, postloader installation will be updated (after confirmation).

oneek2o advanced support
* USB Access for HOMEBREW (see historii.txt for important notices)
* Multiple nand support for different region games
* Built in game cache rebuilder (partially implemented, see historii.txt)

Uneek+DI game browser (see historii.txt)
* Support covers
* Support title vote

USB Loaders forwarder
* Support cfg, gx and wiiflow (actually wiiflow crash)
* Support covers
* Support title vote
* Support ios selection

DML gamecube games
* Support covers
* Support title vote
* Support ios selection
* Can copy games from USB to SD before execute them

Homebrew:
* HB Channel replacement: It can be used to browse homebrew application, with it own interface. 
* Dangerous homebrews can be hidden
* Full support for meta.xml arguments and all other tags.
* It support subfolders (see notes)
* Can browse SD and USB device (FAT32 on first\active partition)
* WiiLoad support (straight, compressed dol, zip archieve)

Channels:
* Nand emulation (ciosx\waninkoko on slot 249)
* AHBPROT is need for real nand browsing (otherwise ios249 is used)
* Wii System Channel replacemente: Can browse and run Channels, WiiWare and VC.
* Can run Titles from real and emulated NAND on SD or USB with folder support
* Titles can be sorted voted and\or hiddened
* Support interactive application sorting
* Sort titles by vote\name
* Titles filters (System channels\wiiware\neogeo\c64... etc)
* Fast titles search
* Download title icons from wiitdb
* Alternate nand folder support (other that classic root)</long_description>
<no_ios_reload/>
</app>